Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Clean it.
نظفه.
I'll clean it for you.
سأقوم بتنظيفه لك.
I didn't know you offered this service.
لم أكن أعلم أنك تقدم هذه الخدمة.
Customer is queen.
الزبون هو الملكة.
Madam, are you awake?
سيدتي هل أنت مستيقظة؟
(What?)
(ماذا؟)
(It's him.)
(إنه هو.)
Drink up!
اشرب!
You lost again.
لقد خسرت مرة أخرى.
Bottoms up!
من الأسفل إلى الأعلى!
(I barely drink any.)
(أنا بالكاد أشرب أيًا منها.)
(Why do I feel so wasted?)
(لماذا أشعر بهذا القدر من الضياع؟)
(I should get freshened up.)
(ينبغي لي أن أستعيد نشاطي.)
Shi Yue, where are you?
شي يوي، أين أنت؟
What's my glasses doing here?
ماذا تفعل نظارتي هنا؟
Come on! Drink up!
هيا! اشرب!
Come on.
تعال.
Hurry.
عجل.
Have a drink.
تناول مشروب.
You call this a drink?
هل تسمي هذا مشروبا؟
Get a bigger shot!
احصل على لقطة أكبر!
Drink up.
اشرب.
Drink.
شرب.
Another one.
واحد آخر.
I caught you.
لقد أمسكت بك.
Glasses thief.
سارق النظارات.
Pretty lady, you got it all wrong.
سيدتي الجميلة، لقد فهمت الأمر بشكل خاطئ.
These are my glasses.
هذه نظارتي.
These are your glasses.
هذه نظاراتك
Come on!
تعال!
Same model. It must be fate.
نفس النموذج. لا بد أن يكون القدر.
Have a drink.
تناول مشروب.
Let's be friends.
دعونا نكون أصدقاء.
What fate?
ما هو المصير؟
Is she your client?
هل هي عميلتك؟
You'd rather drink with her and not me?
هل تفضل أن تشرب معها وليس معي؟
(Client?)
(عميل؟)
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Carry on.
حمل.
Why are you leaving?
لماذا تغادر؟
Forget her.
انساها.
Come on.
تعال.
I'll drink with you.
سأشرب معك.
Where were you just now?
أين كنت للتو؟
The restroom.
الحمام.
Come on.
تعال.
Here.
هنا.
Drink up!
اشرب!
Come on!
تعال!
(Drinking Wine, Dancing Night)
(شرب النبيذ، ليلة الرقص)
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
Another shot!
طلقة اخرى!
(The youngsters' flirting skills are less than underwhelming these days.)
(مهارات المغازلة لدى الشباب ليست مخيبة للآمال هذه الأيام.)
(What a joke.)
(يا لها من مزحة.)
(Did he)
(هل فعل)
(just call me his client?)
(فقط اتصل بي عميله؟)
Had a nice sleep?
هل كان لديك نوم لطيف؟
Hmm?
همم؟
Do you really have to stare at me?
هل حقا يجب عليك أن تحدق بي؟
Breakfast is ready.
الفطور جاهز.
(Oh my.)
(يا إلهي.)
(This can't be more wrong.)
(هذا لا يمكن أن يكون أكثر خطأ.)
(How did I end up with a host?)
(كيف انتهى بي الأمر مع مضيف؟)
Over there.
هناك.
(Of the 36 strategies,)
(من بين الاستراتيجيات الـ 36)
(fleeing is the sound one.)
(الهروب هو الصوت الواحد.)
It's not much to borrow an outfit.
ليس من الصعب استعارة الزي.
My shirt got dirty.
لقد اتسخ قميصي.
I need to borrow this.
أحتاج إلى استعارة هذا.
Certainly, Madam.
بالتأكيد سيدتي.
Are you
أنت
actually
في الحقيقة
the host?
المضيف؟
How do you know?
كيف علمت بذلك؟
But I don't like that title here.
لكنني لا أحب هذا العنوان هنا.
You may call me Lu Xingchen.
يمكنك الاتصال بي لو Xingchen.
The outfit looks good on you.
الزي يبدو جميلا عليك.
I'll pay up at the club.
سأدفع في النادي.
Consider this outfit bought.
فكر في هذا الزي الذي اشتريته.
Don't get wasted if you can't handle it.
لا تضيع وقتك إذا لم تتمكن من التعامل مع الأمر.
And how would you make money if people don't drink?
وكيف يمكنك كسب المال إذا كان الناس لا يشربون؟
We don't make a lot selling alcohol.
نحن لا نربح الكثير من المال من بيع الكحول.
What we sell
ما نبيعه
is the service package.
هي حزمة الخدمة.
It's not worth flexing.
لا يستحق الأمر التباهي.
Satisfying every client
إرضاء كل عميل
is our motto.
هو شعارنا.
(He seems proud of his job.)
(يبدو أنه فخور بعمله.)
Why do I get this feeling
لماذا أشعر بهذا الشعور؟
that you look familiar?
هل تبدو مألوفا؟
Is this the typical playboy troupe?
هل هذه هي فرقة بلاي بوي النموذجية؟
So frosty.
بارد جداً.
Someone broke your heart?
هل كسر أحد قلبك؟
You keep your clients' info confidential, right?
أنت تحافظ على سرية معلومات عملائك ، أليس كذلك؟
Certainly.
بالتأكيد.
The door is over there.
الباب هناك.
Sorry.
آسف.
(Clyton) (I am Gu Liusu.)
(كليتون) (أنا غو ليوسو.)
(I am 30 this year.)
(عمري 30 سنة هذا العام.)
(I founded the hit jewelry brand known as Graceful Line.)
(أسست علامة المجوهرات الشهيرة المعروفة باسم Graceful Line.)
(Due to my being pretty, capable, and single,)
(بسبب كوني جميلة، وقادرة، وعازبة)
(there are plenty of bad comments about my character.)
(هناك الكثير من التعليقات السيئة حول شخصيتي.)
(The gossip is not unlike the accident last night.)
(القيل والقال لا يختلف كثيرا عن الحادث الذي وقع الليلة الماضية.)
(They won't hinder my pace.)
(لن يعيقوا خطواتي.)
(However,)
(لكن،)
(the only thing that captivates me)
(الشيء الوحيد الذي يأسرني)
(Gu Liusu) (is the taste of success.)
(جو ليوسو) (هو طعم النجاح.)
(Gu Liusu, Founder of GL Group)
(جو ليوسو، مؤسس مجموعة GL)
Ms. Gu, you are right on time.
السيدة جو، لقد وصلتِ في الوقت المناسب.
It seems I have a stalker here.
يبدو أن هناك مطارد هنا.
Nice outfit.
زي جميل.
The president of OA Jewelry wants to book next month's haute couture.
يريد رئيس شركة OA Jewelry حجز عرض الأزياء الراقية الشهر المقبل.
No.
لا.
Ms. Gu, please sign this.
السيدة جو، من فضلك وقعي على هذا.
Ms. Gu, your latte.
السيدة جو، لاتيه الخاص بك.
Leave it in my office.
اتركه في مكتبي.
Okay.
تمام.
Morning meeting in 15 minutes.
اجتماع الصباح بعد 15 دقيقة.
Okay, Ms. Gu.
حسنًا، السيدة جو.
Okay.
تمام.
♪The ticking clock hands♪
♪ عقارب الساعة تدق ♪
♪Even that silent high-pitched noise♪
♪حتى هذا الضجيج الصامت عالي النبرة♪
Shark.
سمك القرش.
Enjoying the sun?
هل تستمتع بالشمس؟
♪What exactly is peace?♪
♪ما هو السلام بالضبط؟♪
Did we forget to get that client's contact info?
هل نسينا الحصول على معلومات الاتصال الخاصة بهذا العميل؟
♪All I want is a moment of calm♪
♪كل ما أريده هو لحظة من الهدوء♪
So,
لذا،
we worked all night and even lost a piece of clothing...
لقد عملنا طوال الليل وحتى فقدنا قطعة من الملابس...
♪Those silent screams trapped inside♪
♪تلك الصرخات الصامتة المحاصرة في الداخل♪
♪The deeper I sink♪
♪كلما غرقت أعمق♪
♪The deeper I sink, Mayday♪
♪كلما غرقت أعمق، يا ماي داي♪
♪My breath clutches my throat♪
♪أنفاسي تخنق حلقي♪
♪I barely made it through today♪
♪لقد تمكنت بالكاد من تجاوز اليوم♪
♪This is my trauma♪
♪هذه هي صدمتي♪
Ms. Gu, your coffee.
السيدة جو، قهوتك.
(My Bestie)
(صديقتي المفضلة)
Where were you yesterday?
أين كنت بالأمس؟
You didn't even answer my calls.
لم تجيب حتى على مكالماتي.
Don't you love me anymore?
هل لم تعد تحبني بعد الآن؟
Were you with a guy?
هل كنت مع رجل؟
Tang Baozhu, are you a fortune teller?
تانغ باوزو، هل أنت عرافة؟
Come on.
تعال.
I am your bestie, you know.
أنا صديقك المفضل، كما تعلم.
Spill it.
انسكبه.
The truth is, I got drunk last night.
الحقيقة هي أنني شربت حتى الثمالة الليلة الماضية.
I forgot all the important stuff.
لقد نسيت كل الأشياء المهمة.
No way!
مستحيل!
Was he...
هل كان...
that mediocre?
هذا المتوسط؟
Can someone mediocre even do that?
هل يمكن لشخص عادي أن يفعل ذلك؟
Do what?
افعل ما؟
A host.
مضيف.
A what?
ماذا؟
Why were you messing with a guy like that?
لماذا كنت تتلاعب مع رجل مثل هذا؟
That really was an accident.
لقد كان هذا حادثا حقا.
It is a bit unlucky though.
إنه أمر سيئ الحظ بعض الشيء.
Let me rescue you.
دعني انقذك.
The day after tomorrow is my engagement party.
بعد غد هو حفل خطوبتي.
By then, all the guests will be from powerful families.
وبحلول ذلك الوقت، سيكون جميع الضيوف من عائلات قوية.
I'll introduce you to some top-tier suitors.
سأقدم لك بعض الخاطبين من الدرجة الأولى.
My heart is only set on making money.
قلبي يهدف فقط إلى كسب المال.
I'll attend the party on time.
سأحضر الحفلة في الموعد المحدد.
Forget about the men.
انسي الرجال.
Fine.
بخير.
I'll stop here.
سأتوقف هنا.
Meeting.
مقابلة.
Honey.
عسل.
(Lu Jianhua, President of Xinghan Group)
(لو جيان هوا، رئيس مجموعة Xinghan)
Are you ready?
هل انت مستعد؟
(Tang Baozhu)
(تانغ باوزهو)
(His Fiancée) I have been ready for a long time.
(خطيبته) أنا مستعدة منذ زمن طويل.
Then let's go.
إذن دعنا نذهب.
And your son? Have you settled things with him?
وابنك هل اتفقتم معه؟
Relax, he'll definitely be there.
استرخي، فهو بالتأكيد سيكون هناك.
Mr. Xingchen.
السيد شينغتشن.
I'm from Xinghan Group.
أنا من مجموعة شينغهان.
Your father's personal assistant.
مساعد شخصي لوالدك.
My name is Mo Li.
اسمي مو لي.
Mr. Lu instructed me
لقد أرشدني السيد لو
to take you to pick out your suit for the party.
لأخذك لاختيار البدلة الخاصة بك للحفلة.
I'm not going.
انا لا اذهب
I told you,
أخبرتك،
I don't want to see that gold digger.
لا أريد أن أرى هذا الباحث عن الذهب.
(Mo Li) Having a wedding for a second marriage?
(مو لي) هل تخططين لحفل زفاف للمرة الثانية؟
(Secretary of the President) She should be embarrassed.
(سكرتير الرئيس) يجب أن تشعر بالحرج.
Leave the chores to the servants.
اترك الأعمال للخدم.
Leave it to them.
اترك الأمر لهم.
Perfect.
ممتاز.
Do me a favor.
افعل لي معروفا.
Your father said
قال والدك
the engagement party will be full of elites.
حفل الخطوبة سيكون مليئا بالنخب.
He also wants you to meet them early.
ويريدك أيضًا أن تلتقي بهم في وقت مبكر.
Meet them?
التقي بهم؟
(Lu Xingchen) It is his own engagement party.
(لو شينغتشين) إنه حفل خطوبته الخاص.
(Heir of Xinghan Group) Yet, it carries his personal agendas.
(وريث مجموعة شينغهان) ومع ذلك، فإنه يحمل أجنداته الشخصية.
Pathetic, right?
مثير للشفقة، أليس كذلك؟
Anyway,
على أي حال،
from now on, all matters of you taking over Xinghan Group
من الآن فصاعدًا، كل ما يتعلق بتوليك مجموعة شينغهان
will be handled by me.
سيتم التعامل معه من قبلي.
Mr. Mo, you really are dedicated.
السيد مو، أنت حقا مخلص.
I've passed on the message.
لقد نقلت الرسالة.
There is work to be done.
هناك عمل ينبغي القيام به.
I'll go now.
سأذهب الآن.
I'm not scolding you.
أنا لا أوبخك.
Mr. Xingchen, a message for you.
السيد شينغتشين، رسالة لك.
(Shi Yue: Xingchen,)
(شي يو: شينغشن،)
(news of your dad remarrying)
(خبر زواج والدك مرة أخرى)
(is all over town now.)
(في كل أنحاء المدينة الآن.)
The address for the fitting...
عنوان التركيب...
Did he leave it?
هل تركها؟
He did, Mr. Xingchen.
لقد فعل ذلك، السيد Xingchen.
Take me there later.
خذني هناك لاحقا.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
(So eager to invite me?)
(هل أنت حريص جدًا على دعوتي؟)
(I'll go meet this gold digger myself.)
(سأذهب لمقابلة هذا الباحث عن الذهب بنفسي.)
(Lu Jianhua and Tang Baozhu)
(لو جيان هوا وتانغ باوزهو)
Mr. Li.
السيد لي.
Mr. Lu.
السيد صن
Congratulations, Mr. Lu.
مبروك السيد لو.
Please come inside.
من فضلك ادخل إلى الداخل.
Mr. Lu.
السيد صن
Did Xingchen get the notice?
هل حصل Xingchen على الإشعار؟
Yeah, he did.
نعم لقد فعل.
That kid has been running wild abroad.
لقد كان هذا الطفل يركض في الخارج.
Now that he is back,
الآن وقد عاد،
you'll need to teach him some manners.
سوف تحتاج إلى تعليمه بعض الأخلاق.
Don't worry, Mr. Lu.
لا تقلق يا سيد لو.
I'll make sure he learns.
سأتأكد من أنه يتعلم.
Mr. Lu.
السيد صن
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Congratulations.
مبروك.
Congratulations, Mr. Lu.
مبروك السيد لو.
- Please come inside. - Alright, let's go.
- من فضلك ادخل إلى الداخل. - حسنًا، دعنا نذهب.
The preparations were rushed.
لقد تم الاستعداد بشكل سريع.
I've explained everything.
لقد شرحت كل شيء.
A cynical rich kid, huh?
طفل غني ساخر، أليس كذلك؟
I'm basically
انا اساسا
just playing myself, right?
فقط ألعب بنفسي، أليس كذلك؟
Our mission is...
مهمتنا هي...
To take down the gold digger.
لإسقاط حفار الذهب.
Our goal is...
هدفنا هو...
To seduce Tang Baozhu.
لإغواء تانغ باوزهو.
I memorized her dress design.
لقد حفظت تصميم فستانها.
We'll act accordingly.
سوف نتصرف وفقا لذلك.
Okay.
تمام.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Mr. Xingchen.
السيد شينغتشن.
There are a lot of guests tonight.
هناك الكثير من الضيوف الليلة.
Be sure to behave properly.
تأكد من التصرف بشكل صحيح.
What are you, a cop?
ما أنت، شرطي؟
Don't be nosy.
لا تكن فضوليًا.
When does the party start?
متى يبدأ الحفل؟
In about...
في حوالي...
Half an hour.
نصف ساعة.
Congratulations.
مبروك.
Thanks for coming today.
شكرا لحضورك اليوم.
You look absolutely stunning.
أنت تبدو مذهلة تماما.
Bestie.
صديقتي المفضلة.
Bestie!
صديقي المفضل!
You finally made it!
لقد نجحت أخيرا!
Of course I'd come.
بالطبع سآتي.
If I didn't, someone else would've stolen my bestie.
لو لم أفعل ذلك، لكان شخص آخر قد سرق صديقتي المفضلة.
No way that would happen.
لن يحدث ذلك بأي حال من الأحوال.
Are you here for my wedding
هل أنت هنا لحضور حفل زفافي؟
or to mourn me?
أو تحزن علي؟
What are you saying?
ماذا تقول؟
Touch wood.
ألمس الخشب.
Don't jinx it.
لا تجلب الحظ السيئ.
I have another dress.
عندي فستان آخر.
Go change into it.
اذهب لتغييره.
Tang Baozhu.
تانغ باوزهو.
You're the one getting engaged,
أنت من سيخطب
so why should I steal the spotlight?
فلماذا يجب أن أسرق الأضواء؟
It's fine. I like it this way.
لا بأس، أنا أحب ذلك بهذه الطريقة.
Bestie.
صديقتي المفضلة.
Did you forget our childhood promise?
هل نسيت وعد طفولتنا؟
We said we'd be the prettiest ones at each other's engagement party.
لقد قلنا أننا سنكون الأجمل في حفل خطوبة بعضنا البعض.
I look pretty good, don't I?
أنا أبدو جيدًا جدًا، أليس كذلك؟
Go on, hurry!
إذهب، بسرعة!
Alright, alright.
حسناً حسناً.
Where is it?
أين هي؟
Over there.
هناك.
Quick, go.
سريعا، اذهب.
The black widow style, with the pearl gown.
أسلوب الأرملة السوداء، مع ثوب اللؤلؤ.
She is the one.
إنها هي.
Tang Baozhu.
تانغ باوزهو.
I won't allow you to marry Lu Jianhua!
لن أسمح لك بالزواج من لو جيانهوا!
I am in love with you!
انا احبك!
(They are here for Baozhu?)
(هل هم هنا من أجل باوزهو؟)
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
=Starlit Bloom=
=ازهار النجوم=
♪But I can't escape♪
♪لكنني لا أستطيع الهروب♪
♪The memories of you♪
♪ذكرياتك♪
♪The harder I try to forget♪
♪كلما حاولت أن أنسى♪
♪The more you come back to me♪
♪كلما عدت إلي أكثر♪
♪Two hearts once in love collide and shatter into pieces♪
♪قلبان كانا في حالة حب تصادما وتحطما إلى قطع♪
♪How can I piece myself together again?♪
♪كيف يمكنني أن أجمع نفسي مرة أخرى؟♪
♪Funny, isn't it?♪
♪مضحك، أليس كذلك؟♪
♪Only after losing you did I see your love was worth keeping♪
♪فقط بعد أن فقدتك رأيت أن حبك يستحق الاحتفاظ به♪
♪I hate myself for not being brave, for not trying♪
♪أكره نفسي لعدم كوني شجاعًا، لعدم محاولتي♪
♪For letting you slip away into the crowd with my own hands♪
♪لأني سمحت لك بالانزلاق إلى الحشد بيدي ♪
♪Guess we just met at the wrong time♪
♪أعتقد أننا التقينا في الوقت الخطأ♪
♪What's left of our love is nothing but ashes♪
♪ما تبقى من حبنا ليس سوى رماد♪
♪Look at us♪
♪انظر إلينا♪
♪Like two planets that were never meant to meet♪
♪مثل كوكبين لم يكن من المفترض أن يلتقيا♪
♪Colliding across the sky♪
♪الاصطدام عبر السماء♪
♪At the wrong time, I found the one I loved most♪
♪في الوقت الخطأ، وجدت الشخص الذي أحببته أكثر♪
♪Does that still count as luck?♪
♪هل لا يزال هذا يعتبر حظًا؟♪
♪Look at us♪
♪انظر إلينا♪
♪Like two planets that were never meant to meet♪
♪مثل كوكبين لم يكن من المفترض أن يلتقيا♪
♪Colliding across the sky♪
♪الاصطدام عبر السماء♪
♪Maybe we were never meant to be♪
♪ربما لم يكن من المفترض أن نكون معًا♪